http://www.phins.com/privacy.html

Privacy Statement for
Phins.com
Phins.com
has created this privacy
statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses the information gathering and
dissemination practices for this Web site.
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.
Your IP address is automatically logged by our webservers and is used only to created usage statistics.
No IP information collected here is shared with any other parties.
Cookies
At this time, our site uses cookies only to track survey results.
These cookies expire after one month and only contain enough information to determine if and when you last voted in one of our surveys.
Advertisers
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here
Personal Information
With the exception of our mailing lists and private message board, this Web site does not request or collect any information that personally
identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.
For our mailing lists and private message board, the only information we collect is a valid email address.
The purpose of collecting your email address is only to identify and validate your participation in those forums.
We do not share ANY personal
information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes, other than those described in the paragraph above .
External Links
This site contains links to other sites.
Phins.com
is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
The security consists of strict control over access to all information using standard web security measures.
The only personal information we store are email addresses and access to those addresses is limited to the director of Phins.com.
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us here.
